A Guide to the David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, RG 49 FA1506
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, RG 49
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
FA1506
27.14 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the David Rockefeller Estate, January 2019. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact a RAC archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetical, in 29 series, primarily by subject/topic.
Scope and Contents
The 1997-2000 general files chronicle continued management of the philanthropic affairs of David Rockefeller.
Over the years the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national and international levels through their foundation activities as well as their individual personal giving. Major interests include: physical and mental health, conservation, education, economics, international relations, politics, population, religion, social welfare, the visual and performing arts, cultural exchange programs, and economic and social development of underdeveloped areas. While David Rockefeller naturally began to reduce his public schedule and activities in the later years of his life and career, the vast scope and breadth of his philanthropic interests continued in much of the same subject matter.
The general files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records as well as documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate, newspaper clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, audio tapes, and printed material.
- David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1997-2000, 49; 27.14 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 record storage box.
  - Audiovisual Materials, A
    Moving Images
    - Colleges - SUNY - University at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government - The Citizen Laureate Awards Honoring Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 2000 April 13 (T1)
  - A, 1997-2000; 1; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - A - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Scope and Contents
      American Simmental Association; Florida Stewardship Foundation; Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA); Genetically Modified Food Collaboration; Maine Beef Industry Council; National Cattlemen's Beef Association Political Action Committee.
    - Agriculture - American Farmland Trust, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appeals - Domestic - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4-8)
    - Appeals - Foreign - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Arts, 1997-2000; 2; 4.18 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes
    - Arts - A-L, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
      Advertising Council, Inc.; Alliance for Young Artists and Writers, Inc.; American Friends of Flamenco; American Institute of Architects (AIA); Arkansas Arts Center Foundation; Art and Literature from Latin America, Inc.; Art in General; Art Institute of Chicago; Art Show; Art Worx; Arts and Business Council, Inc.; Arts Connection; Banff Center for the Arts; Beyond Baroque; Big Apple Circus; Burchfield - Penny Art Center; CEC International Partners; Candid Arts Trust; Century Association Archives Foundation; Checkerboard Foundation, Inc.; Clark Arts Center; Clark Center for Japanese Arts Center; Classical America (Arthur Ross Awards); Community Programs in the Arts; Country Roads; Dia Center for the Arts; Drawing Center; Elysium Between Two Continents; En Garde Arts, Inc.; Exit Art; Frank Diaz Escalet; Friars Foundation; Freer Gallery of Art; Friends of the Statue of Liberty and Ellis Island, Inc.; High Five Tickets to the Arts; Institute of Contemporary Art; International Foundation for Art Research; Japanese Art Association; John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts; The Kitchen.
    - Arts - M-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Martha Stewart Living, Mississippi Commission for International Cultural Exchange, Inc., Municipal Art Society, National Academy of Design, National Design Awards, New York International Festival of the Arts, Nubreed Synergy of the Arts, Owings-Dewey Fine Art, Papp Project, Performing Arts Center of Los Angeles, Performing Arts Center of Purchase College, Peruvian Institute of Contemporary Art, Dubncan Phillips Awards, President's Committee on the Arts and the Humanities, Princess Grace Foundation, PS 1 Contemporary Arts Center (MoMA), Public Art Fund, Public Broadcasting Service on Cuba with Ballet Hispanico, Repertorio Espanol, Christine Roussel Studios, Russian Arts Foundation, Spanish Colonial Arts Society, Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences, Theatreworks USA Corp., Three Thousand Years of Chinese Painting, Cynthia Van Leeuwen, Westchester Arts Council, Joan Whalen Fine Art, Craig Whitaker Architects, Charlotte White's Salon de Virtuosi.
    - Alliance for the Arts, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Americans for the Arts, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - American Associates of the Royal Academy Trust, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Americans United to Save the Arts and Humanities, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Center for Arts Education, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Century Association, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Children's Art Carnival, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Lincoln Center, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Jazz at Lincoln Center, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Duncan Phillips Awards, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Public Art Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Studio in a School, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - World Monuments Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Appraisals - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Christie's
    - Books - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Bernice Kert - biography of Abby Aldrich Rockefeller. Starry Night.
    - Dance - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Gleich Dances, Kozlov Dance International, Sarsota Ballet, School of American Ballet, Unique Project, Inc., Vaganova Ballet Academy.
    - Dance - American Ballet Theatre, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Dance - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Dance - New York City Ballet, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Films - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Center for Cultural Inquiry, New York Film Project.
    - Galleries - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Adelson Galleries, Inc., Arranz Gallery, Feuerman Studios, David Findley, Inc., Galerie Schmit, Gerald Peters Gallery, C. Grimaldis Gallery, Islands of Maine Gallery, La Guilde Graphique, Max Protech Galleries, SVO Art, Tate Gallery, Elizabeth Wang Gallery.
    - Libraries - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
      American Trust for the British Library, George Bush Presidential Library Foundation, Camden Public Library, Claverack Free Library, Germantown Library, Greenwich Library (in memory of Stephanie Edgell), Livingston Free Library, Northeast Harbor Library, Richard Nixon Library and Birthplace Foundation, Ronald Reagan Presidential Library, Seal Harbor Library Association, Warner Library of the Tarrytowns.
    - Libraries - Library of Congress, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Libraries - Library of Congress - Henry A. Kissinger Chair in Foreign Policy and International Relations, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Libraries - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Libraries - New York Public Library, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Libraries - Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Institute, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Memorials - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      The Duke Ellington Memorial Fund
    - Museums - A-C, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Abbe Museum, American Air Museum in Britain, American Craft Museum, American Friends of Blerancourt, Inc., American Friends of the British Museum, American Friends of the Hermitage Museum, American Museum in Britain, American Museum of the Moving Image, Amon Carter Museum, Art Resources Transfer, Baltimore Museum of Art, The British Museum, Buffalo Bill Historical Society, Chilhuly Museum, Children's Museum of Manhattan, the Chinati Foundation.
    - Museums - D-J, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Dahesh Museum, Friends of Wild Bird (Margaret and Nat Owings home), Fuller Museum of Art, Great Harbor Maritime Museum, High Museum of Art, Hudson River Museum, Huguenot Heritage, Independent Curators International, International Glass Museum, International Museum of Peace and Solidarity, Intrepid Museum Foundation, Isamu Noguchi Garden Museum, Japanese American National Museum.
    - Museums - K-L, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Katonah Museum of Art, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Lowe Art Museum
    - Museums - M, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Massachusetts Museum of Contemporary Art, Menil Collection, Metropolitan Museum of Art, Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, Museo de Arte de Ponce, Museum for African Art, Museum of the American Cowboy, Museum of American Financial History, Museum of Art Rhode Island School of Design, Museum of the Americas Foundation, Inc., Museum of Automobiles, Inc., Museum of the Hudson Highlands, Musuem of International Folk Art, Museum of Modern Art in Lima, Museum of Television and Radio, Mystic Seaport Museum.
    - Museums - N-R, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      National Academy Museum and School of Fine Arts, National Cowgirl Museum and Hall of Fame, National Museum of Western Art, National Museum of Women in the Arts, Native Art Museum, New Bedford Whaling Museum, New Orleans Museum of Art, New York City Police Museum, Philadelphia Museum of Art, Plimoth Plantation, Portland Museum of Art, Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts, Frederic Remington Art Museum, "Rockefeller Museum" Museum in Jerusalem.
    - Museums - S-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      San Antonio Museum of Art, Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Latin American Art, Skyscraper Museum, Seattle Art Museum, South Street Seaport Museum, Southwestern Research Station (American Museum of Natural History), Statens Museum fur Kunst, The Studio Museum in Harlem, Tangier American Legation Museum Society, Trust for Museum Exhibitions, Wadsworth Atheneum Museum of Art, Winterthur Museum, Garden and Library.
    - Museums - American Friends of the Israel Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Museums - American Museum of Natural History, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Museums - The Brooklyn Children's Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Museums - El Museo del Barrio, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Museums - Farnsworth Center for the Wyeth Family in Maine, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Museums - The Frick Collection, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Museums - Wendell Gilley Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Museums - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Museums - The International Council - Museum of Modern Art, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Museums - Merchant's House Museum, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Museum of American Financial History, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Museums - Museum of the City of New York, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Museums - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Museums - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Museum of Modern Art Mission Statement.
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art Archives, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Museums - Orange County Museum of Art, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Museums - Queens Museum of Art, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Museums - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Magazine, Spring Woods Gallery.
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - Archives of American Art, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - Libraries, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - National Gallery of Art, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - National Museum of the American Indian, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 8, Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - Museums - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Music - A-C, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
      Aldeburgh Festival of Music and the Arts, American Friends of the Concert Orchestra of Amsterdam, Arcady Music Festival, Association Culturelle et Musicale Memory, Bar Harbor Music Festival, Boston Symphony Orchestra (Tanglewood Music Center), Boys Choir of Harlem, Cantana Singers, Inc., Caramoor Center for Music and Arts, Chateauville Foundation, Children's Orchestra Society.
    - Music - D-L, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Encorp Concert Series, English Chamber Orchestra Society of America, Fund for La Fenice, Fundacion Isaac Albeniz, Golden Gate Opera Company, Harlem Youth Chamber Orchestra, Hudson Opera House.
    - Music - M-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Carole King Making Music With Friends, Manhattan School of Music, Metropolitan Opera, Midori and Friends, Mt. Desert Festival of Chamber Music, Music Assistance Fund, Musicians Assistance Program, New York City Opera, Orpheus Chamber Orchestra, Performing Arts Against AIDS, Perlman Music Program, Pro Musicis, Saint Luke's Chamber Ensemble (Orchestra), September Concert Foundation, Society of Singers Emergency Relief Fund, Songwriters' Hall of Fame, Washington Opera, Washington Square Music Festival, Westminster Choir College of Rider, Young Audiences, Young Concert Artists, Inc.
    - Music - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Music - Carnegie Hall Society, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Music - The Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Music - New York Philharmonic, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Music - Young Audiences, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Paintings - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Vincente Carillo-Batalla. Joshua Dorman. Benjamin Donald McCready. Javad Mirjavadov. Mongerson-Wunderlich. Richard Whitney.
    - Poetry - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      The Pushkin Legacy
    - Publications - A-C (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Publications - D-L (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Publications - M-Z (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Publications - Culture and Civilization of China (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Publications - University of Michigan Press (Box 11, Folder 4)
      A Civil Enconomy - Transforming the Marketplace in the 21st Century.
    - Restorations - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Blaine House, Historic House Trust of New York City, Friends of Akrotiri, Middleton Place Foundation, New York Restoration Project, Ormond Beach Historical Trust, Inc., Save Venice, Inc., Versailles Foundation, Inc., Edith Wharton Restoration.
    - Restorations - American Friends of Versailles, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Restorations - Friends of Olana, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Restorations - George C. Marshall International Center, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Restorations - New York Landmarks Conservancy, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Restorations - Ormond Beach Historical Trust, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Restorations - Preservation League of New York State, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sculpture - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Louise Meiere Dunn. Susan Geissler Studio. Leondardo da Vince's Horse. Evie Marlin.
    - Theatre - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Apollo Foundation, GOH Productions, HB Playwrights Foundation and Theatre, National Actors Theatre, The New Victory Theater, The Public Theater, Repertorio Espanol, Shakespeare Guild, Theatre for a New Audience.
  - B-C, 1997-2000; 3; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - B - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - C - Miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Civic, 1997-2000; 4; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Civic - A-B, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      America-Israel Friendship League, American Battle Monuments Commission, American Jewish Historical Society, Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Berkshire Taconic Community Foundation, British American Chamber of Commerce, Business Leaders for Sensible Priorities
    - Civic - C, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      CEO Summit, Charles E. Innisss St. Joseph Franciscan House, Churchtown Fire Company, Citizen's Housing and Planning Council, Citizens Network, Civic Air Patrol - Downeast Patrol Composite Squadron, Conservancy for Historic Battery Park, Corporate Social Solutions, CREDO Housing Development Corporation.
    - Civic - D-L, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Daughters of the Elks, Eastport Area Chamber of Commerce, Empire Expo Center, Empower America, Forest Hill Homeowners, Inc., Anne Frank Center USA, Future Wave, Global Green USA, HELP USA, Holocaust Claims Processing Office, Holocaust Human Rights Center of Maine, Human Resource Service, Inc., Human Rights Watch, Independent Institute, INFORM, Institute for Urban Design, Integritas, International League for Human Rights, Isle Au Haut Lighthouse Fund, Keep America Beautiful, League of Women Voters of the City of New York Education Fund, Linlithgo Fire Company, Livingston Pumper Co. No. 1.
    - Civic - M, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Maine Community Foundation, Millennium Auction, Millennium Committee of New York, Mt. Pleasant Police Benevolent Association.
    - Civic - N-R, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      National Arts Club, National Conference for Community and Justice, National Executive Service Corps, National Institute of Social Sciences, National Policy Association, New York Council of the Navy League, New York Genealogical and Biographical Society, New York League of Conservation Voters, New York Society of Association Executives, People for the American Way, Robin Hood Foundation.
    - Civic - S-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Sleepy Hollow Millennium Clock, Sleepy Hollow St. Patrick's Day Parade Committee, Southern Columbia County Ambulance Squad, Inc., Spirit of Christmas, Strategic Alliance Fund, Summer Residence Association (Town of Mt. Desert), Taghkanic Fire Co., Third Millennium, Town Hall Fire Company, Harry S. Truman Fund, United States-Mexico Chamber of Commerce, WA Shrine Temple, WAVE, Westchester County Association, Inc., White House Correspondent's Dinner, White House Millennium, Work In America Institute.
    - Citizens Against Government Waste, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Fifth Collaboration, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Robin Hood Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Chamber of Commerce - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Japanese Chamber of Commerce and Industry of New York.
    - New York City - A-G, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Alliance for Downtown New York, Inc., Avenue Association, Bronx 2000's Big City Forest, Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, Cab Watch, Chairman of the Leadership in Tourism Award, Citizens Budget Commission, Citizens Union Foundation, City Hall Conservancy, Endeavor, Fund for the City of New York.
    - New York City - H-N, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Harlem Educational Activities Fund, Inc., HELP USA, Historic Landmarks Preservation Center, 100 Year Association of New York, Millennium Committee, NYC 2000, Miracle Makers, Inc., New 42nd Street, Inc., New Market Company, New York Cares, New York City Chapter of the American Society for Industrial Security, New York City Public-Private Initiatives, Inc., New York Initiative, Inc., Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York.
    - New York City - O-S, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      One Hundred Black Men, Park Avenue Malls Holiday Lighting Project (Salute to the Seasons Fund), Publicolor, David Rockefeller Fellows, Second Chance
    - New York City - T-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Trust for Public Land, Volunteer Consulting Group.
    - New York City - Abyssinian Development Corporation, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - New York City - Citizens Committee for New York City, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - New York City - Community Gardens, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Community Service Society of New York, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - New York City - New York City Partnership, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - New York City - New York City Police Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - New York City - New York City Public-Private Initiatives, Inc, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - New York City - Regional Plan Association, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - United States Government - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      White House Endowment Fund, White House Fellows Foundation
  - Clubs, 1997-2000; 5; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Clubs - A-M, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      1925 F Street Club, Inc., Alfalfa Club, American Driving Society, Bohemian Grove Club, Cercle de l'Union Interalliee, Century Association, Chicago Club, City Club of New York, Fly Club, Garden Club of Mount Desert, Harbor Club, Harvard Club of New York City, Maidstone Club, Metropolitan Republican Club (MET Club).
    - Clubs - N-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      New York Yacht Club, Northeast Harbor Fleet, River Club, Seal Harbor Yacht Club, Sierra Club, Union League Club, University Club.
    - Knickerbocker Club, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1997-2000; 6; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Contributions, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Commercial Ventures, 1997-2000; 7; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Commercial Ventures - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Banking - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Banco Mercantil, Venezuela. Bank Dagang Nasiona Indonesia, Bank of Japan, Bankers Trust Company, Export-Import Bank of Japan, Heiner Hartwich, International Monetary Fund.
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - A-Z, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
  - Conservation, 1997-2000; 8; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Conservation - A-F, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Acadia Wildlife Foundation, American Himalayan Foundation, Ancient Forest International, Archaeological Conservancy, Audubon New York, Birdlife International, Butterfly Discovery Park, Center for Enviornmental Research and Conservation, The Rene Dubos Center for Human Environments, Inc., Forest Hill Park, Frenchman Bay Conservancy, Friends of Blue Hill Bay, Friends of the Rockefeller State Park Preserve.